var quizData = [
    {
        question: "What is the name of Jon Snow's direwolf?",
        options: [
            "Ghost",
            "Grey Wind",
            "Graham",
            "Ricky"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Ghost",
    },
    {
        question: "What's the name of Lysa Arryn's way-too-old-to-be-nursing son?",
        options: [
            "Ned",
            "Robin",
            "Edmore",
            "Tyrion"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Robin",
    },
    {
        question: "What's the name of the explosive that gave the Lannisters the edge in the Battle of Blackwater?",
        options: [
            "Wildfire",
            "Dragonfire",
            "Godsfire",
            "Pantsonfire"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Wildfire",
    },
    {
        question: "How is \"The Queen Of Thorns\" more commonly known?",
        options: [
            "Cersei Lannister",
            "Margaery Tyrell",
            "Olenna Tyrell",
            "E Jarvis Thribb"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Olenna Tyrell",
    },
    {
        question: "What is Pycelle's official title in the Red Keep?",
        options: [
            "Master of Coin",
            "Games Maester",
            "Lord Commander of the Kingsguard",
            "Grand Maester"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Grand Maester",
    },
    {
        question: "Which Lannister song signalled doom at the Red Wedding?",
        options: [
            "The Rains Of Castermere",
            "A Golden Crown",
            "The Assassin's Dagger",
            "Tales Of Topographic Oceans"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "The Rains Of Castermere",
    },
    {
        question: "What piece of fencing advice did Jon Snow give to Arya Stark? \"Stick them with the…\"",
        options: [
            "\"Prickly end\"",
            "\"Sharp end\"",
            "\"Futtocks End\"",
            "\"Pointy end\""
        ],
        correctAnswer: "\"…Pointy end\"",
    },
    {
        question: "Who said, \"Some day I'm gonna put a sword through your eye and out the back of your skull\"?",
        options: [
            "Theon Greyjoy",
            "Shae",
            "Arya Stark",
            "The Mountain"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Arya Stark",
    },
    {
        question: "Who was burned alive on Drogo's funeral pyre?",
        options: [
            "Khal Drogo",
            "Mirri Maz Duur",
            "Maris Piper",
            "Septa Mordane"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Mirri Maz Duur",
    },
    {
        question: "Who said, \"If you ever call me sister again, I'll have you strangled in your sleep\"?",
        options: [
            "Annie Lennox",
            "Meg White",
            "Catelyn Stark",
            "Cersei Lannister"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Cersei Lannister",
    }
]

export default quizData;